softsyshosting.com 2018-09-12

# Softsys Hosting - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to SoftSys Hosting; maintaining your trust is paramount to us.

This Statement about privacy policy discloses the information practices for SoftSys, from what type of information about our Web sites’ users is gathered and tracked, to how the information is used, shared or otherwise processed offline. Furthermore, this Statement applies to SoftSys Hosting Websites and not third party websites or websites hosted on SoftSys Hosting servers for their end customers / users.

##   
Collection of Personal Information

In the course of serving our customers, Softsys Hosting receives, stores and transmits data that may be private or sensitive. Some of these data are provided to us by our customers in order that we may provide service. Examples of these data include your personal name, address, telephone number, business name and payment information.  
Other data is created and stored by Softsys Hosting as we configure and maintain customers' service. Examples of this data include your choice of service and logs of your account activity. Softsys Hosting also uses cookies to track usage of our website in aggregate.  
In case you decide to make payments via ACH bank transfer, you agree to Plaid’s Privacy Policy - we use Plaid’s services to perform verification of ownership of bank account. If you use ACH bank transfer through our system, you agree that information will be treated in accordance with Plaid’s privacy policy. You also authorize granting Plaid the right, power and authority to access and transmit the data as reasonably necessary for Plaid to provide the Service to you. 

##   
Updating Your Personal Information

Personal information that is provided by you to SoftSys during signing up for a service with us or creating an account with us can be updated by you at any time from our self-service billing portal. You will have full control to update all fields of your personal information to ensure that it is correct & up to date from time to time. In case you have any trouble with this access, you can get in touch with our billing department to regain the access.

## Deleting Your Personal Information

SoftSys Hosting will retain your personal information for as long as there is any active service associated with your account AND that we are not explicitly asked by customer to delete their personal data (entire account). Your personal information will help us to serve you and contact you when you have any active services associated with us. Additionally, we will require your personal information for accounting & finance perspective (Invoices & transactions history). In case you wish to have us delete your personal information, please get in touch with our billing department & we will process it promptly.

## Exporting Your Personal Information

You are the owner of your personal information and are free to port it anywhere else. If you wish to export your personal information with us, please get in touch with billing department and we will provide an export of your personal information in JSON format.

## Consent About Getting Contacted

You will be able to select if you want us to contact you for marketing purposes during creating an account with us. You will also be in control of changing your initial consent at any time from self service billing portal.

##   
Withdrawing Consent

You will be able to withdraw your consent at any time regarding us to contact you for marketing purposes at any time from self service billing portal.

## Personal Information Retention

We will be retaining your personal information for a period of 7 years after inactivity (inactivity is defined as customer not having any active services with us, have not logged into their account with us or have not attempted to login to their account with us). If you want us to immediately remove your information from our databases after inactivity, please contact billing department from your registered email on file.

##   
Disclosure of Customer Information and Communications

Softsys Hosting will not disclose its customers' personal and account data unless we have reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, make contact with, or bring legal action against someone who may be causing harm or interfering with the rights or property of Softsys Hosting, Softsys Hosting's customers, or others, or where 

Softsys Hosting has a good faith belief that the law requires such disclosure.

Softsys Hosting also will not, except for reasons stated below, disclose to third parties the contents of any electronic mail or other electronic communications that Softsys Hosting stores or transmits for its customers.

The circumstances under which Softsys Hosting will disclose such electronic customer communications are when: 

1) It is necessary in order to provide service to the customer;  
2) t is necessary to protect the legitimate interests of Softsys Hosting and its customers; and   
3) It is required to cooperate with interception orders, warrants, or other legal process that Softsys Hosting determines in its sole discretion to be valid and enforceable; and   
4) It is necessary to provide a law enforcement agency when the contacts are inadvertently obtained by Softsys Hosting and appear to pertain to the commission of a crime.

##   
Modification of Customer Information

Customers may modify their personal information from members / client portal or by emailing billing[@]softsyshosting.com or by opening a helpdesk ticket.  

Did you find this article useful?   __ __ 0 out of 0 people found this article useful.
